Slocum mss., 1955-2012 LMC 2681
Lilly Library
- XX. Additions (Box 111)
  - Mrs. Anibas, Richter materials (Box 129)
  - Oskar Richter (Box 129)
  - Oskar Richter, Gretz Schutter, Richter (Box 129)
  - Richter's Anchor Puzzles: Jerry Slocum's Correspondence with Oskar Richter and Erich Schneider (Rudolstadt), 2005 (Box 129)
  - Schneider, Erich, 1971 (Box 129)
  - Erich Schneider (Rudolstadt) (Box 129)
  - Erich Schneider and Helene (Box 129)
  - Dic Sonneveld, Searches (Box 129)
  - R. Thiele (Box 129)
  - Anker Correspondence, 1994 (Box 129)
  - J.S. History, Letters, Contacts (Box 129)
  - Baker, Pat (Box 129)
  - Barton, Les, Anchor Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Brockman, Martin (Box 129)
  - Brokenshire Collection (Box 129)
  - Claus Ahlers, Richter Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Anker Stone Puzzle Collection of James Dalgety (Box 129)
  - Dalgety, Richter Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Gillen, Anchor Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Gillen, Marcel, Anker (Box 129)
  - Gitt, Carlo, Anchor Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Goers, Gunner, 1902; 1909 (Box 129)
  - Hahn, Renate and Otto, Richter History (Box 129)
  - Hajek, Peter, Anchor Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Hess, Richter Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Anker Stone Puzzle Collection of Dick Hess, May 2005 (Box 129)
  - Hordern Anker Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Isaacs, Stan (Box 129)
  - Frans de Jonge, Catalogs, Price Lists, etc. (Box 129)
  - De Jonge, Frans (Box 129)
  - De Jonge, Frans, Email Correspondence (Box 129)
  - De Jonge, Frans, Not Sent to D.G. (Dieter Gebhardt) (Box 129)
  - Keil, Dr. Manfred (Box 129)
  - Koppel, Bob (Box 129)
  - Leeflang, Henk, 2010 (Box 129)
  - Linkola, Matti, Anker Puzzles (Box 129)
  - McFarland, Pat, SandR Anchor Ads (Box 129)
  - Martinson, Brian (Box 129)
  - Mensenkamp, Dieter, Anker (Box 129)
  - Pedersen, Ole Poul, Anchor Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Modern Anchor Puzzles, 1996-2005, from the Collection of Harold Razer (sic) (Box 129)
  - Raizer, Richter Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Raizer, Harold (Box 129)
  - Anker Stone Puzzle Collection of Harold Raizer, May 2005 (Box 129)
  - Wolfgang Schneider, Anker Collection (Box 129)
  - Schouten, J. (Box 129)
  - Schule, Burkhard, Anker Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Schweitzer, Bernhard, Printer's Marks, Anchor Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Selms Letters (Box 129)
  - Selms, Ad van, Correspondence (Box 129)
  - Ad van Selms, Hague (Box 129)
  - Selms, Ad van, Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Anchor Stone Puzzle Collection of Ad van Selms, April 2005 (Box 129)
  - Selms Correspondence, 2010-2011 (Box 129)
  - Shortz, Richter Puzzles (Box 129)
  - Slooten, Jan (Box 129)
  - Tvrdik, Stanislav (Box 129)
  - Tucker, Rick, SandR Catalog (Box 129)
  - De Vreugd, Frans, Anker Correspondence (Box 130)
  - Werff, Correspondence, 2007-2011 (Box 130)
  - Werff, Jan van der, Printer's Marks (Box 130)
  - Wessel, George, Block Sets (Box 130)
  - Waite, Correspondence, 2008 (Box 130)
  - Waite, William, Anchor (Box 130)
  - Wiezorke, Bernhard, Anker, 2004 (Box 130)
  - Walk, Wolfgang (Box 130)
  - Yoshigahara, Nob (Box 130)
  - Anker Puzzles, Slocum Puzzles (Box 130)
  - Anchor, Composite (Box 130)
  - Anchor Puzzles, Wanted, Master (Box 130)
  - Anchor Puzzles, Slocum's Collection (Box 130)
  - Slocum Anker Puzzle Collection (Box 130)
  - Anchor, Puzzle Lists (Box 130)
  - Anker Box and Book Covers (Box 130)
  - Slocum, Anchor Stone Puzzles History, 1978 (Box 130)
  - Anchor Book, Earliest Drafts, 1978 (Box 130)
  - Anchor, Compendium, Cover Drafts, 1978 (Box 130)
  - The Complete Anchor Puzzle Book, 1979 (Box 130)
  - Book Outline (Box 130)
  - Anchor Book Outline and Data (Box 130)
  - Anchor Puzzle Book Outline, 2005 (Box 130)
  - Questions/Stats (Box 130)
  - Richter's Anchor Puzzle Box and Book Puzzles, Bound Drafts, (26) (Box 130)
  - Intro, Foreword, Acknowledgements, (3 folders) (Box 130)
  - Anchor Book, Outline (Box 130)
  - Richter Puzzles, Start (Box 130)
  - F. Ad. Richter's Puzzles (Box 130)
  - Puzzles, 1911-1913 (Box 130)
  - Raizer, Hard Problems and Easy (Box 130)
  - Puzzle Book, 1914-1918 (Box 130)
  - Between Wars, 1919-1938 (Box 130)
  - After Rebirth, 1989 (Box 130)
  - Design Puzzles (Box 130)
  - Making Puzzles (Box 130)
  - Ads and Praise (Box 130)
  - Selling Puzzles (Box 130)
  - Competitors, Copies (Box 130)
  - Pictorial Index (Box 130)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book First Rough Draft, Dec. 6, 2007 (Box 131)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Vol. 1, Ch. 2-6, Rough Draft, Dec. 29, 2007 (Box 131)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Vol. 2, Ch. 7-11, Rough Draft, Jan. 8, 2008 (Box 131)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Vol. 1, Ch. 1-6, Rough Draft, Jan. 13, 2008 (Box 131)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Rough Draft, Jan. 29, 2008 (Box 131)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Rough Draft #1, Feb. 1, 2008 (Box 131)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Rough Draft #2, Mar. 1, 2008; (3 bound volumes) (Box 131)
  - Sonneveld, Dic, Corrections, Draft #2 (Box 131)
  - Ad van Selms, Draft #2, Corrections, 4/08 (Box 131)
  - Hardy, George, Corrections, Draft #2 (Box 131)
  - Gebhardt, Dieter, Corrections, Draft #2 (Box 131)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Rough Draft #3, May 15, 2008; (2 bound volumes) (Box 131)
  - Draft #3 to DC (Box 131)
  - D. Gebhardt, Corrections, Anchor Draft #3 (Box 131)
  - Sonneveld, Corrections, Anchor Draft #2 (Box 131)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Rough Draft #3A, April 17, 2008 (Box 131)
  - Anchor Book, 3A, Corrections (Box 131)
  - Anchor Book, 4A, Corrections (Box 131)
  - Sonneveld Corrections (Box 132)
  - Raizer Corrections, 2008 (Box 132)
  - Gebhardt Corrections, March 2009-March 2010 (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Draft #5 and #6 (Box 132)
  - Gebhardt Corrections, 2011 (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Draft #6, 2011 (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Bound Draft (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Corrections, Proof (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Pre-proof (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Proof, 2011 (Box 132)
  - Norton Starr, APB, Proof (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Proof, Harold Raizer (Box 132)
  - Anchor Puzzle Book, Proof, George Hardy (Box 132)
  - Dic Sonneveld, Proof, Corrections, (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - Ad van Selms, Proof, Corrections (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Bound Proof, Ad van Selms (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Marked Proof for Jerry (Box 132)
  - Gebhardt Corrections, (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Credits (Box 132)
  - New Ads, Add to Book (Box 132)
  - Corrections, 11/13/2011-2/2012 (Box 132)
  - German Translation, D. Gebhardt, 3/10/2012 (Box 132)
  - Text, Drafts (Box 133)
  - #8 Anchor Pictorial Book, Ad van Selms (Box 133)
  - Add Problems to APB (Box 133)
  - Problems for #6, #2, #13, #32 (Box 133)
  - New Anchor Factory, 1994-1995 (Box 133)
  - The Anchor Puzzle Book Rough Draft #5, Jan. 17, 2009 (Box 133)
  - J. Botermans' Anker Puzzle Photos, (2 folders) (Box 133)
  - Photo List, Anker Puzzles (Box 133)
  - Anker Layout Slides (Box 133)
  - Botermans, Jack, Correspondence (Box 133)
  - Katalog der Anker-Bausteine, 2008; (large binder) (Box 133)
  - Rudolstadt Puzzle Collection and Photos (Box 134)
  - Richter's Villa Rudolstadt (Box 134)
  - Printer's Country Code (Box 134)
  - Production, Old Data in List (Box 134)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 134)
  - F. Ad Richter and Co. Anchor Stone Puzzles, Problems (Box 134)
  - The Fifteen Puzzle, Vol. 1 and Vol. 2 (Box 134)
  - The World's Best Puzzles, BandN Project (Box 134)
  - 2D Paper Puzzles (Box 134)
  - Paper Puzzle Book, Send To Lists (Box 134)
  - Compendium of Keychain Puzzles, First Draft, Apr. 4, 2011 (Box 134)
  - Stewart Coffin, Puzzle Craft Manuscript (Box 134)
  - The 45 IPP Invitees That Have Attended 15 or More IPPs Compiled by Jerry Slocum, Aug, 9, 2012 (Box 134)
  - The 631 Invited Puzzlers That Have Attended IPP #1 through IPP #31 Compiled by Jerry Slocum, Aug. 9, 2012; (2 copies) (Box 134)
  - Correspondence with Jerry Slocum (Box 135)
  - Copyrighted Puzzle Diagrams, (6 folders) (Box 135)
  - Coffin, Stewart (Box 135)
  - Hess, Dick (Box 135)
  - Kamei, Akio (Box 135)
  - Catalogs and Price Lists (duplicates), Anchor Puzzles (Box 135)
  - Mobley, Bill (Box 135)
  - Tomii, Yoichi (Box 135)
  - CITES Certificate (Box 135)
  - Puzzle Patents (Box 135)
  - R.W. Skinner Auctioneers (Box 135)
  - Torii Dexterity Puzzles Design Sheet (Box 135)
  - British Library Reproductions (Box 135)
  - Indiana University Alumni Magazine Treasures of the Lilly Library, Mar/Apr. 2011 (Box 135)
  - Johnson Smith and Co., Supplementary Catalogue, 1915; (photocopy) (Box 135)
  - Slocum Anchor Puzzle Descriptions (Box 137)
  - Slocum and Richter, Game Catalogs, Microfilm (4) (Box 138)
  - Interview by Eric Elliott of Jerry Slocum, for IUB Libraries Development Office, Mar. 26-27, 2012; Audiotapes (2) (Box 138)
  - Anchor Puzzle Book, DVDs (2) (Box 138)
  - Anchor Puzzle Book, CD-Rs (5) (Box 138)
  - Stewart Coffin, CD-Rs (3) (Box 138)
  - Catalogs and Price Lists (duplicates), Anchor Puzzles (Box 138)
  - Puzzle Animations, CD-R (Box 138)
  - Cutting, Dissecting and Nesting, CD-R (Box 138)
  - The World's Best Paper Puzzles, Prototype (Box 139 (Oversize))
  - V-Cubes, Flat Puzzle Boxes (Box 139 (Oversize))
  - Sketch Portrait of Jerry Slocum, Gift from Anatoly Kalinin, Aug. 2012 (Box 140 (Oversize))
  - Framed Puzzle Image (Box 140 (Oversize))
  - Framed Midwest Living article, including blurb on Lilly Library Slocum Room (Box 140 (Oversize))
  - John Rausch Materials (Box 140 (Oversize))
    - Coffin Puzzles in Slocum Collection, (2 folders) (Box 135)
    - AGCA, 1995 (Box 135)
    - Byzantium magazine (Box 135)
    - Articles (Box 135)
    - Ephemera Society (Box 135)
    - Antique Toy World Games and Puzzles, Whitehill (Box 135)
    - Bulletin Le Vieux Papier (Box 135)
  - Stewart Coffin Materials (Box 135)
    - Stewart Coffin Binder (Box 135)
  - Allan Boardman Materials (Box 135)
    - Correspondence - Boardman (Box 136)
    - Boardman Keeper Examples (Box 136)
    - Puzzle Diagrams (Box 136)
    - Photographs (Box 136)
    - Publications, (3 folders) (Box 136)
    - Jerry Slocum's Directory of Puzzle Collectors and Puzzle Sellers (Box 136)
    - Puzzles and Solutions, (4 folders) (Box 136)
    - Puzzle Lists (Box 136)
    - George Washington Folding Puzzle, Souvenir of 1st Japanese Puzzle Party, 1989 (Box 136)
    - Catalogs, (2 folders) (Box 136)
    - Puzzle Articles (Box 136)
    - Reference Guide to Ishi Press Puzzles, Oct. 1993 (Box 136)
    - New Knot Diagrams, as Modified and Made by Allan Boardman, 2000 (Box 136)
    - Mechanical Puzzle Classification, Jerry Slocum, Jul. 1991 (Box 136)
    - Excerpts from Pacioli's De viribus quantitadis (Box 136)
    - Puzzle Party Info (Box 136)
    - The 15 Puzzle Sheet Music (Box 136)
    - The Puzzle World Who Where Alphabetical List of Names, 1986 (Box 136)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 136)
  - Additions, 2014 (Box 141)
    - Exchange Puzzle (Box 141)
    - IPP #17 (Box 141)
    - IPP #17 Lessons and Data (Box 141)
    - IPP #17 Attendees and Invite Database (Box 141)
    - IPP #17 Exchange (Box 141)
    - 14th Exchange (Box 141)
    - IPP #14 (Box 141)
    - IPP #14 Exchange (Box 141)
    - Party and Exchange Schedule and Info (Box 141)
    - IPP #15 Japan (Box 141)
    - IPP #15 Tokyo, Apr. 15, 1995 (Box 141)
    - Tokyo - Maps, Puzzle Hunting (Box 141)
    - IPP #15 Exchange Tokyo (Box 141)
    - MIT PP, 2/95 (Box 141)
    - IPP #16 (Box 141)
    - 16th IPP (Box 141)
    - IPP #16 Exchange (Box 141)
    - IPP #12 Exchange Tokyo (Box 141)
    - Hakone (Box 141)
    - Japan - 12th IPP (Box 141)
    - Japan - Puzzle Hunting (Box 141)
    - 12th IPP Tokyo (Box 141)
    - IPP #10.1, 1989 (Box 141)
    - 13th IPP Holland, 1993 (Box 141)
    - Cube Day (Box 141)
    - 13th IPP Correspondence (Box 141)
    - 13th IPP (Box 141)
    - IPP #13 Exchange Netherlands, 1993 (Box 141)
    - 9th PP Tokyo (Box 141)
    - Japan (Box 141)
    - 10th Puzzle Party (Box 141)
    - 10th IP Party (Box 141)
    - IPP #10 Exchange (Box 141)
    - 10 ½ IPP, April 1990 (Box 141)
    - IPP #11 Exchange (Box 141)
    - 11th Puzzle Party Attendance (Box 141)
    - Registration List (Box 141)
    - Invitations (Box 141)
    - Hotel (Box 141)
    - Puzzle Party #1, Apr. 1, 1978 (Box 141)
    - Puzzle Party #2, May 5, 1979 (Box 141)
    - Puzzle Party #3, Ap. 12, 1980 (Box 141)
    - Puzzle Party #4, Apr. 25, 1981 (Box 141)
    - Puzzle Party #5, 1982 (Box 141)
    - 6th Puzzle Party, Apr. 2, 1983 (Box 141)
    - 7th Party (Box 141)
    - Nichols Party and Trip (Box 141)
    - Nichols Party (Box 141)
    - 7.75 Mini Party (Box 141)
    - Other Puzzle Parties (Box 141)
    - Puzzle Party #8 (Box 141)
    - 8th Invitation (Box 141)
    - Photos - 8th IPP (Box 141)
    - Address List Puzzle Party (Box 141)
    - IPP 18, (5 folders) (Box 142)
    - Visas - Russia (Box 142)
    - IPP 19, (7 folders) (Box 142)
    - IPP 20, (5 folders) (Box 142)
    - Exchange Survey (Box 142)
    - Marriott (Box 142)
    - Hess Chinese Puzzles (Box 142)
    - Kamei Exhibit (Box 142)
    - Trip Schedule: Japan, China, Mongolia, Documents, 2001 (Box 142)
    - IPP 21, (11 folders) (Box 142)
    - Postcards (Mongolia) (Box 142)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 142)
    - IPP 22 Design Competition, Antwerp, 2002 (Box 143)
    - IPP 22, (9 folders) (Box 143)
    - IPP 23, (12 folders) (Box 143)
    - IPP 24, (13 folders) (Box 143)
    - IPP 24 Souvenir Book (Box 143)
    - IPP 24 Mongolia, China Photos (Box 143)
    - IPP 25, (4 folders) (Box 144)
    - IPP Future Management (Box 144)
    - Design Competition Changes (Box 144)
    - Yoshigahara Award (Box 144)
    - St. Petersburg, (2 folders) (Box 144)
    - IPP Exchange Puzzles Book? (Box 144)
    - Exchange. Back Room 197-A (Box 144)
    - Photos (mounted) (Box 144)
    - Yoshigahara Award, (2 folders) (Box 145)
    - Coffin Award (Box 145)
    - IPP 26, (7 folders) (Box 145)
    - IPP 27, (16 folders) (Box 145)
    - IPP 28, (16 folders) (Box 146)
    - IPP 29, (13 folders) (Box 146)
    - IPP 30, (8 folders) (Box 146)
    - IPP 30, (16 folders) (Box 147)
    - IPP 31, (11 folders) (Box 147)
    - Scans - photos/negatives (Box 148)
    - IPP 13-18 (Box 148)
    - IPP 19-23 (Box 148)
    - IPP 8 (Box 148)
    - IPP 9 (Box 148)
    - IPP 15 (Box 148)
    - IPP 16 (Box 148)
    - IPP 17 (Box 148)
    - IPP 18 (Box 148)
    - IPP 19 (Box 148)
    - IPP 20 (Box 148)
    - IPP 21 (Box 148)
    - IPP 22 (Box 148)
    - IPP 23 (Box 148)
    - IPP 24 (Box 148)
    - IPP 25 (Box 148)
    - IPP 26 (Box 149)
    - IPP 27 (Box 149)
    - IPP 28 (Box 149)
    - IPP 29 (Box 149)
    - IPP 30 (Box 149)
    - IPP 31 (Box 149)
    - IPP History 1-31 New Talk (Box 149)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 149)
    - Photos Needed (Box 150)
    - History of IPP 1-16 Slocum Talk (Box 150)
    - History of IPP 1-16 CFF Article (Box 150)
    - IPP History (Box 150)
    - Local P.P.s (Box 150)
    - IPP History Slides 1-16 (Box 150)
    - Dr. Leung Tangram (Box 151)
    - Tangram Problems (Box 151)
    - Isabel Wei Translations (Box 151)
    - Leung, S.K. Tangram (Box 151)
    - Dic - Tangram vs. Tangram (Box 151)
    - Tangram - Word History (Box 151)
    - Hill, Thomas - The Word Tangram (Box 151)
    - Tangram Word Origin (Box 151)
    - Tangrams in Schools (Box 151)
    - Read, Ron (Box 151)
    - Singmaster's Tangram Books and Comments (Box 151)
    - Catalogs, 1890-1936; (45 folders) (Box 152)
    - Yeung, Man-Shun Tangrams (Box 153)
    - Tangram Books (Box 153)
    - Japan - Seikado Bunko (Box 153)
    - Tangram Articles (Box 153)
    - Cox - Trangram (Box 153)
    - Trangram and Tangram (Box 153)
    - Tangram Today (Box 153)
    - HSBC Tangram Ads (Box 153)
    - HSBC Correspondence (Box 153)
    - Books (Box 154)
    - Bibliography Tangrams (Box 154)
    - Chinese Tangram Books (Box 154)
    - American and European Books (Box 154)
    - U.S. - Cox, 1817 (Box 154)
    - U.S. - Goodrich (Box 154)
    - - Punqua, 1839 (Box 155)
    - - Chapman Sci. Amusements, 1844 (Box 155)
    - U.S. -, 20TH Century Neset (Box 155)
    - U.S. - Misc. (Box 155)
    - Argentina Early Puzzles (Box 155)
    - Austria Early Puzzles (Box 155)
    - Denmark Early Puzzles (Box 155)
    - Denmark (Box 156)
    - England Early Puzzles (Box 156)
    - U.K. - Davenporte (Box 156)
    - U.K. - Wallis (Box 156)
    - U.K. - Lowry, 1818 (Box 156)
    - Lowry - A Key to Chinese Puzzle (Box 156)
    - U.K. Books (Box 156)
    - U.K. - Taylor (Box 156)
    - U.K. - Paine and Simpson (Box 156)
    - U.K. Dudeney, Bell, 20th Century (Box 157)
    - Finland Early Puzzles (Box 157)
    - France Early Puzzles (Box 157)
    - French (Box 157)
    - Allizeau, Les Metamorphoses (Box 157)
    - Chapelle, Grand, 1895 (Box 157)
    - France (Box 157)
    - French Puzzles (Box 158)
    - Germany Early Puzzles (Box 158)
    - German (Box 158)
    - India Early Puzzles (Box 158)
    - Italy Early Puzzles (Box 158)
    - German (Box 158)
    - Italy Books (Box 159)
    - Italian (Box 159)
    - Netherlands Early Puzzles (Box 159)
    - Russia (Box 159)
    - Russia Early Puzzles (Box 159)
    - Spain Early Puzzles (Box 160)
    - Sweden Early Puzzles (Box 160)
    - China Puzzles (Box 160)
    - China-Japan Mulberry, 1813 (Box 161)
    - China Puzzles (Box 161)
    - China, 1816 (Box 161)
    - China Puzzles (Box 161)
    - China Tangram, 1813 (Box 161)
    - China Puzzles, 1823-1861; (several bound manuscripts) (Box 162)
    - China - Shanghai Manuscripts and other bound manuscripts (Box 163)
    - China Puzzles -, 1885-2005; undated; (several bound manuscripts) (Box 164)
    - Chinese Puzzles, (multiple folders and bound manuscripts) (Box 165)
    - Japanese Puzzles, (multiple folders and bound manuscripts) (Box 165)
    - Japanese Puzzles, (multiple photocopied and bound manuscripts) (Box 166)
    - Additional International Puzzles, (multiple photocopied and bound manuscripts) (Box 166)
    - Chinese Puzzles, (multiple photocopied and bound manuscripts) (Box 167)
    - Tangram Book, (multiple bound drafts) (Box 167)
    - IPP 26 Boston (Box 167)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 168)
    - Tangram Problems Supplements (not in books) - Master Copy (Box 168)
    - Les Difficultes Chinoises - Masters (Box 168)
    - Chinese Puzzles, (multiple photocopied and bound manuscripts) (Box 168)
    - Anchor Stone Puzzles - research materials (Box 169)
    - Czech (Box 169)
    - Printing Costs (Box 169)
    - Importing (Box 169)
    - Anker Stones (Box 169)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 169)
    - IPP 24 (Box 170)
    - Catalogs - Richter, Original (Box 170)
    - Anchor Catalogs and Other Materials (Box 170)
    - Dr. Leung Materials (Box 171)
    - Leung, S.K. Correspondence (Box 171)
    - Anchor Materials, 1950s-1990s (Box 171)
    - Anchor Puzzle Sheets, Lists (Box 171)
    - Competitors to Richter (Box 171)
    - Lotts Brick Co., London (Box 171)
    - Foreign Anker Puzzles (Box 171)
      (Swedish, Finnish, Dutch)
    - Anchor Copies Puzzles (Box 171)
    - Affiliates - Richter (Box 171)
    - Patents (Box 171)
    - Lilienthal (Box 171)
    - The Anchor Puzzle Book First Rough Draft, Dec. 6, 2007 (Box 172)
    - Chinese Puzzle Materials (Box 172)